http://www.blueridgepublishing.com/p/privacy-policy.html

Updated for GDPR 2018
Copyright by Michelle Jones, CEO of Blue Ridge Publishing, Inc.
We Have ALWAYS Respected Your Privacy
We are committed to providing our readers and members with the utmost privacy and security. We abide by all industry guidelines and consistently monitor our management and operating methods in order to maintain our valued reputation and integrity. We do NOT collect personal information from any of our visitors or members and we do NOT sell, rent or give away our member subscription lists to anyone, for any reason. Unlike many online companies we do NOT send out separate email advertisements to our subscribers and never will. Ever!
Membership is ALWAYS FREE
Our free monthly ezine, Living a Better Life®, can only be received by email subscription and membership. Members may unsubscribe at any time. NO PERSONAL INFORMATION is collected. Email addresses are only collected for our OPT-IN subscription list to send our monthly ezine. By signing up for our free monthly ezine you agree that we have permission to contact you via electronic mail with article and site updates, that may or may not include sponsor and/or advertiser promotions. This ezine is mailed once a month (sometimes bi-monthly) and subscribers receive no further mailings from us other than occasional holiday greetings, special announcements, or reminders regarding the site or our budgeting class.
Our mailing list provider YMLP.com has also updated their privacy policy according to the 2018 GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation).
Minimal Advertising
To help cover the costs of maintaining our Websites (BetterBudgeting, Frugal Family Recipes, GrocerySavingTips, CookieClubRecipes, and AllinTheFamilyTreeResearch) and to keep them forever free for the online community we feature minimal advertising through Google and Amazon that could be of great interest to our readers in their search for helpful information and resources.
Our advertiser's privacy policies are managed completely separate from us and we have been notified that they are up to date with GDPR.
NO Cookies for Us
Cookies are NOT collected on our Websites or in our monthly ezine and never have been. Our technology is simply not that advanced because we just want YOU to follow US. Not the other way around.
Contact Information
Our Websites abide by the laws and guidelines of the Internet. We welcome any inquiries as to the use of visitor and membership information or company methods and practices. If you have any questions or comments regarding this privacy policy, please e-mail us at editor@betterbudgeting.org.
Privacy Policy Copyright © by Michelle Jones
CEO of Blue Ridge Publishing, Inc.
Email ThisBlogThis!Share to TwitterShare to FacebookShare to Pinterest
Home
Subscribe to:
Posts (Atom)
